( operatic tenor bellowing):
♪ MORNING'S HERE ♪
♪ THE MORNING'S HERE ♪
♪ SUNSHINE IS HERE ♪
♪ THE SKY IS CLEAR ♪
♪ THE MORNING'S HERE ♪
♪ THE MORNING'S HERE... ♪
HEY!
DO YOU HAVE TO DO THAT?
IT'S SATURDAY!
OH, COME ON.
MORNING'S HERE!
♪ MORNING'S HERE ♪
♪ THE MORNING'S HERE ♪
♪ SUNSHINE IS HERE ♪
♪ LA-DA-DA
DAH-DAH-DAH-DAH-DAH... ♪
I HATE THIS APARTMENT!
( door slams )
I HATE THE COLOR OF THESE WALLS.
I HATE THE FACT THIS PLACE
STILL SMELLS LIKE BIRD.
I HATE THAT SINGING GUY.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I LOVE THAT GUY.
♪ MORNING'S HERE ♪
♪ MORNING IS... ♪
STOP IT!
I WILL KILL YOU.
GOD.
I HATE THE FACT
THAT MY ROOM IS SO SMALL.
HEY, I HAVE ALL
THE SPACE I NEED.
JUST DO WHAT I DID.
MONICA, YOU DON'T EVEN
HAVE A BED.
YOU SLEEP IN A BALL
ON THE FLOOR.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM REALLY TIRED OF
YOUR BELLYACHING, OKAY?
I'VE WORKED REALLY
HARD AT MAKING THIS
A NICE PLACE FOR US TO LIVE.
I KNOW.
I'M SO SORRY.
I'M SORRY, OKAY?
THIS IS A GREAT
APARTMENT.
SHUT UP! THIS
PLACE IS A HOLE!
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
OH, BLIMEY!
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'VE GOT AN EARRING.
I KNOW. WHO AM I:
( English accent ):
DAVID BOWIE?
HE DOES THAT?
I DON'T KNOW. WHATEVER.
I THINK IT MAKES YOU LOOK
REALLY DANGEROUS.
OH, I KNOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I NEVER WOULD
HAVE GOTTEN THIS
IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOU.
NO, REALLY.
WHEN I'M WITH YOU, I'M LIKE
THIS-THIS WHOLE OTHER GUY.
I LOVE THAT GUY.
I MEAN, I LOVE YOU,
TOO, A LOT
BUT THAT GUY.
I LOVE THAT GUY.
I LOVE BOTH OF YOU.
YEAH?
( sighs )
I WISH I DIDN'T
HAVE TO GO.
THEN DON'T.
STAY HERE.
JUST DON'T GO
SO SOON TO LONDON.
JUST ONE MORE DAY.
ROSS, PLEASE DON'T
DO THIS TO ME AGAIN.
ONE MORE DAY.
I'D STAY IN A MINUTE
BUT I'VE ALREADY MISSED
SO MUCH OF MY WORK
THEY'D FIRE ME.
SO? THEN YOU COULD STAY
AS LONG AS YOU WANT.
I WISH I COULD.
OH, DON'T-DON'T
START PACKING.
COME ON.
I DON'T THINK
YOU UNDERSTAND PACKING.
I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE IT
TILL THE LAST MINUTE.
THE LAST TIME I PACKED
IN A RUSH, I LEFT MY KNICKERS.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I, UH, I TRIED THEM ON.
YOU DIDN'T!
NO, I DIDN'T.
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE THAT GUY.
( karate yells )
HELLO.
HO, HO, HO!
EXCUSE ME?
YOUR PANTS.
OH, YEAH!
YOU LIKE THEM?
I WENT TO
A USED CLOTHES STORE
AND GOT A BUNCH
OF MATERNITY STUFF.
THESE ARE SO COMFORTABLE.
UH, PHEEBS,
THOSE ARE SANTA PANTS.
WHAT?
SANTA PANTS.
SANTA CLAUS'S PANTS.
NUH-UH.
THEY'RE MATERNITY PANTS.
THEY EVEN CAME
WITH A LIST OF BABY NAMES.
SEE?
THESE NAMES ARE GOOD
AND THESE ARE BAD.
OH.
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS.
SO, HOW ARE THE ELVES?
( goofy voice ):
I DON'T KNOW.
HOW ARE THE...
YOU KNOW.
YOUR CLOTHES AREN'T FUNNY.
HEY, GUYS, WHAT SHOULD
I WEAR TO A KNICKS GAME?
UH, A T-SHIRT THAT SAYS,
"I DON'T BELONG HERE."
YOU HAVE KNICKS TICKETS?
YEAH. MY MOM
GOT MY DAD'S
SEASON TICKETS
IN THE DIVORCE
SO SHE JUST
GAVE THEM TO ME.
APPARENTLY, THEY'RE
PRETTY GOOD SEATS.
OH, MY GOD!
THOSE ARE ALMOST
RIGHT ON THE FLOOR!
DO YOU GUYS WANT THESE?
YEAH!
YEAH, WE DO!
OH, WELL, YOU GOT 'EM.
ALL RIGHT!
JUST GIVE US
OUR APARTMENT BACK.
WHOA! I DIDN'T
SEE THAT COMING.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
( taunting ):
COME ON.
WE KNOW WHAT
THESE ARE WORTH.
WHAT, DO YOU THINK
WE'RE STUPID?
NOT STUPID.
YOU'RE MEANER
THAN I THOUGHT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
FORGET IT, OKAY?
I'M NOT GIVING UP
MY BACHELOR PAD
FOR SOME BASKETBALL SEATS.
YOUR BACHELOR PAD?
HAVE YOU EVEN HAD
A GIRL UP HERE?
NO.
BUT, UH... JOEY HAS
AND I USUALLY TALK TO THEM
IN THE MORNING TIME.
YEAH, YOU DO.
COME ON.
YES, GUNTHER, CAN I GET
TWO CUPS OF CHINO, PLEASE?
GOOD ONE.
HEY, COME ON--
SEASON TICKETS.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS?
FORGET IT. I'M NOT
GIVING UP THE APARTMENT.
LOOK, WHEN I WAS
A LITTLE KID
MY DAD'S COMPANY GAVE
SEASON TICKETS
TO THE NUMBER-ONE
SALESMAN EVERY YEAR.
MY DAD NEVER WON.
OF COURSE, HE WASN'T
IN THE SALES DIVISION
BUT STILL, I NEVER
EVER, EVER FORGOT THAT.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY.
OH, MY GOD.
WE DON'T MAKE ENOUGH
FUN OF YOU ALREADY?
OH, YEAH.
EMILY CONVINCED
ME TO DO IT.
YOU DO KNOW
THAT WHAM! BROKE UP?
( laughing )
YEAH, WELL, I LIKE IT
AND EMILY LIKES IT
AND THAT'S WHAT COUNTS.
SO, UH, HOW ARE
YOU GUYS DOING?
DON'T TRY AND
TALK ALL NORMAL
WITH THAT THING
IN YOUR EAR.
WHERE'S EMILY?
SHE'S SAYING GOOD-BYE
TO HER UNCLE.
MAN, DIDN'T SHE, LIKE,
JUST GET HERE?
YEAH! YEAH!
EASY, TIGER.
I JUST... I HATE THIS SO MUCH.
EVERY TIME I GO PICK HER UP
AT THE AIRPORT
IT'S SO GREAT,
BUT AT THE SAME TIME
I'M THINKING, WELL, I'M GOING
TO BE RIGHT BACK THERE
IN A COUPLE OF DAYS
DROPPING HER OFF.
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO?
THERE'S NOTHING TO DO.
SHE LIVES THERE, I LIVE HERE.
I MEAN, SHE'D HAVE TO MOVE HERE.
SHE SHOULD MOVE HERE.
WHAT?
I COULD ASK HER
TO LIVE WITH ME.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WHY NOT? I MEAN, WHY NOT?
BECAUSE YOU'VE
ONLY KNOWN HER SIX WEEKS.
I'VE GOT A CARTON OF MILK
IN MY REFRIGERATOR
I'VE HAD A LONGER
RELATIONSHIP WITH.
BUT, GUYS, WHEN I'M
WITH HER, IT'S LIKE...
SHE BRINGS OUT
THIS-THIS THIS GREAT SIDE OF ME.
I MEAN, I LOVE HER, YOU KNOW?
AND I LOVE THE MILK!
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO ASK
SOME BRITISH GIRL
TO MOVE IN WITH ME.
JOEY, YOU SAY
THINGS NOW.
LOOK, ROSS, HE'S RIGHT.
EMILY IS GREAT.
SHE'S GREAT
BUT THIS IS TOO SOON.
YOU'RE ONLY GOING TO SCARE HER.
I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT.
NO.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO WRECK IT.
TO GO TOO FAST.
YEAH. NO,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I KNOW YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M NOT GOING
TO DO IT.
THANKS, GUYS.
OKAY, NO PROBLEM.
JUST REMEMBER TO WAKE US UP
BEFORE YOU GO-GO.
OH, IT'S TOO HARD.
TOO HARD!
ALL RIGHT, BOYS--
LAST CHANCE
FOR THE TICKETS.
OTHERWISE, I GIVE THEM
TO MY NEW BOYFRIEND JOSHUA.
NO, THANK YOU.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT.
COME ON, COME ON--
LET'S TRADE.
THE TIMING'S PERFECT.
I JUST CLOGGED THE TOILET!
LOOK, I WANT THOSE
BASKETBALL SEATS
AS MUCH AS YOU DO, OKAY?
BUT WE CAN'T LIVE IN
THE SMALL APARTMENT
AFTER WE'VE LIVED HERE!
DIDN'T YOU EVER READ
FLOWERS FOR ALGERNON?
YES...
DIDN'T YOU EVER READ
SPORTS ILLUSTRATED?
NO, I DIDN'T READ YOURS.
LOOK, COME ON, WE CAN GO
TO THE GAME TONIGHT.
LOOK, THE ONLY WAY I
WILL EVEN CONSIDER THIS
IS IF THEY OFFER A LOT MORE
THAN JUST SEASON SEATS.
BUT IT'S THE KNICKS!
SCREW THE KNICKS!
WHOA...
I DIDN'T MEAN THAT.
I JUST MEANT
THAT THE APARTMENT
IS WORTH SO MUCH MORE.
HUH.
AND THE KNICKS RULE ALL.
YEAH! THE KNICKS
RULE ALL.
HEY, SO ARE YOU
GOING TO DO IT?
NO. NO, WE'RE NOT.
YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE IT'S NOT
AN EVEN TRADE.
LOOK, WHAT IF YOU COULD
KEEP THE APARTMENT
AND GET THE TICKETS?
DONE!
LET ME FINISH.
WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT A BET--
WINNER TAKES ALL.
WE COULD END UP
WITH NOTHING.
OR END UP WITH
EVERYTHING.
OOH, I LIKE THAT.
ALL RIGHT,
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY?
NO!
OH, JUST DO IT!
OH! OH, I'M CONVINCED.
COME ON, MAN.
YOU KNOW
I'D DO IT FOR YOU.
BECAUSE YOU'RE
MY BEST FRIEND.
( sighing )
ALL RIGHT, BUT YOU
CAN'T USE THAT AGAIN
FOR A WHOLE YEAR.
I'M IN.
OOH! THIS
IS SO EXCITING!
OH, GOD, WHAT
ARE YOU GOING TO BET?
OH, OKAY. WELL,
I THINK WE SHOULD
LET PHOEBE DECIDE
BECAUSE SHE'S THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S IMPARTIAL
AND SHE'S SO PRETTY.
OKAY.
UM... OOH, OOH...
OH, I HAVE A GAME!
OH, THIS IS GREAT!
WHAT'S THE GAME,
WHAT'S THE GAME?
WELL,
IT DOESN'T HAVE A NAME.
NO, OKAY: "PHOEBE BALL."
( chuckling )
NO, IT DOESN'T
HAVE A NAME.
UM... OKAY, MONICA,
WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE THING
ABOUT TREES?
THEY'RE GREEN?
GOOD! GOOD!
FIVE POINTS!
ALL RIGHT!
Phoebe:
GREAT! ALL RIGHT
JOEY...
SAME QUESTION.
UH...
OH!
HMM. THEY'RE TALL.
OOH! THREE POINTS.
NO. BOTH FINE ANSWERS
BUT WE WERE LOOKING
FOR "LEAFY."
"LEAFY."
THAT'S NOT EVEN A GAME.
SHUT UP!
WE'RE WINNING.
YOU WANT TO FINISH
THIS RIGHT NOW?
WE GET A DECK
OF CARDS.
HIGH CARD WINS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
FINE. LET'S DO IT.
OOH! I HAVE CARDS.
OH, GOOD.
YEAH! HERE.
OH, NO. THESE
ARE THE TRICK DECK.
OKAY... HERE, YES.
OKAY.
OKAY, YOU GUYS...
YOU GUYS PICK FIRST.
OKAY.
FOUR.
THAT'S A
LOW ONE-NAH!
ALL RIGHT.
PHOEBE, YOU LOOK.
I CAN'T DO IT.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I CAN?!
OKAY, OKAY.
ACE!
( screaming )
WHY ARE YOU SCREAMING
AND HUGGING?
WE WON OUR
APARTMENT BACK!
Joey:
WHAT?
ACE IS HIGH:
JACK, QUEEN, KING, ACE.
NO, ACE IS LOW: ACE,
TWO, THREE, FOUR.
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT, BUT, OOH!
OOH!
LOOKIT! AH!
PICK AGAIN,
PICK AGAIN!
ALL RIGHT, GIMME, GIMME.
OKAY.
COME ON,
APARTMENT!
COME ON, APARTMENT!
( sighing )
( whooping )
I KNOW QUEEN IS HIGH!
AH, NOT AS HIGH AS...
IT WORKED! KING!
WE WIN!
( laughing )
( whooping )
WE PICK AGAIN,
WE PICK AGAIN!
WHY?
I DON'T KNOW.
TICKETS, PLEASE.
( frustrated groan )
THAT'S COURTSIDE, BABY!
( laughing ):
YEAH!
SERIOUSLY, GOOD
GAME, THOUGH!
GOOD GAME...
WHAT ARE THEY
SO MAD ABOUT?
THEY GOT THE
APARTMENT BACK.
NO, THEY DIDN'T.
( door opens and shuts )
HEY.
PACKED WHILE
YOU WERE GONE.
I LEFT SOME KNICKERS
UNDER YOUR PILLOW.
MOVE IN WITH ME.
WHAT?
DON'T BE SCARED.
I-I KNOW IT SOUNDS CRAZY
AND PEOPLE WILL SAY
IT'S TOO SOON
BUT JUST, JUST THINK.
THINK HOW GREAT IT WOULD BE.
OH...
I DON'T KNOW.
( sighing )
OH, LEAVING LONDON. UH...
MY WHOLE FAMILY
LIVES THERE.
MY JOB.
WELL, SO YOU'LL GET
A JOB HERE.
I MEAN, I'M ALWAYS HEARING
ABOUT THEM FOREIGNERS COMING IN
AND STEALING AMERICAN JOBS.
THAT COULD BE YOU.
YEAH, BUT I-IT'S
MY WHOLE LIFE.
YOU COME TO ENGLAND.
NO, I CAN'T.
I WOULD, I REALLY WOULD,
BUT MY SON IS HERE.
I CAN'T LEAVE HIM.
YOU DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANY WAY?
OH, I DON'T THINK SO.
I MEAN, IT WOULD BE DIFFERENT
IF IT WAS WAY INTO THE FUTURE
AND, AND WE WERE GETTING
MARRIED, OR SOMETHING.
WHAT?
OH. NO. NO, RIGHT.
UH, I SHOULDN'T HAVE
SAID "MARRIED."
UH, PLEASE DON'T
GET FREAKY ON ME.
UH... I DIDN'T
MEAN IT.
I TAKE IT BACK.
NO, NO, DON'T.
WHY DON'T WE?
WHY DON'T WE WHAT?
( nervous laugh )
GET MARRIED.
YOU ARE MAD.
NO, NO!
I'M NOT.
IT'S-IT'S-IT'S PERFECT!
I MEAN, IT'S BETTER
THAN YOU JUST MOVING HERE
'CAUSE IT'S US
TOGETHER FOREVER
AND THAT'S,
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
WE'VE ONLY KNOWN EACH
OTHER FOR SIX WEEKS.
I KNOW. SO WHAT?
I MEAN, WHO'S TO SAY?
DOES THAT MEAN
WE, WE CAN'T DO IT?
LOOK, I WAS WITH CAROL
FOR FOUR YEARS
BEFORE WE GOT MARRIED
AND I WOUND UP DIVORCED
FROM A PREGNANT LESBIAN.
I MEAN, THIS...
THIS MAKES SENSE FOR US.
COME ON!
I MEAN, OUR FIRST DATE
WE ENDED UP SPENDING
THE WHOLE WEEKEND IN VERMONT.
I MEAN, LAST NIGHT,
I GOT MY EAR PIERCED.
ME!
( laughing )
IT JUST FEELS RIGHT.
DOESN'T IT?
MY PARENTS ARE GOING
TO BE REALLY MAD.
IS THAT...
ARE YOU SAYING "YES"?
IS THAT "YES"?
YES.
YES!
YES? WE'RE GETTING...?
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED?
OH, MY GOD!
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED!
WE, WE...
COME HERE, COME HERE.
OW!
EMILY, WILL YOU MARRY ME?
YES.
OH, IT'S A BIT SMALL.
DAMN! I THOUGHT THAT WAS GOING
TO BE ROMANTIC AS HELL!
IT WAS.
THOSE WERE, LIKE,
THE BEST SEATS EVER.
OH, YEAH. HEY!
SHOULD WE GIVE THESE
SHIRTS TO THE GIRLS
YOU KNOW, KIND OF LIKE
A PEACE OFFERING?
YEAH. THAT'S VERY NICE.
PLUS, THEY WERE FREE
AND THEY'RE TOO SMALL.
OH... OH, GOD!
HEY, YOU WANT
A BEER?
WHOA!
I KNOW!
OPEN UP! OPEN UP! OPEN UP!
WE'LL DISCUSS IT
IN THE MORNING.
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
WE TOOK OUR
APARTMENT BACK.
I HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH IT.
OKAY. IT WAS MY IDEA
BUT I DON'T FEEL
GOOD ABOUT IT.
OH! OH!
WE ARE SWITCHING BACK
RIGHT NOW.
NO, WE'RE NOT.
WE'RE NOT LEAVING.
WELL, YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO LEAVE SOMETIME
BECAUSE YOU BOTH
HAVE JOBS
AND AS SOON AS YOU DO,
WE'RE SWITCHING IT BACK.
THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO
TO STOP US, RIGHT, JOE?
I DON'T KNOW. I...
WHAT?!
I DON'T WANT TO MOVE AGAIN.
( mumbling )
I DON'T CARE.
THIS IS OUR APARTMENT
AND THEY STOLE--
YOU STOLE!--
OUR APARTMENT.
WE WON THAT APARTMENT
FAIR AND SQUARE TWICE
AND I AM GETTING
IT BACK RIGHT NOW.
I'M GETTING IT
BACK RIGHT NOW!
ALL RIGHT...
WE FIGURED YOU MIGHT
RESPOND THIS WAY
SO WE HAVE
A BACKUP OFFER.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
NO MORE OFFERS.
YOU CAN'T OFFER
ANYTHING TO US.
LET US KEEP THE
APARTMENT AND...
AS A THANK YOU...
RACHEL AND I WILL KISS
FOR ONE MINUTE.
TOTALLY WORTH IT.
THAT WAS ONE
GOOD MINUTE.
GOOD NIGHT.
MEN ARE SUCH IDIOTS.
I KNOW. CAN YOU BELIEVE
SOMETHING THAT STUPID
ACTUALLY GOT US
OUR APARTMENT BACK?
IT'S SO FUNNY TO THINK--
IF YOU HAD JUST DONE THAT
AFTER THE LAST CONTEST
NO ONE WOULD'VE HAD
TO MOVE AT ALL.
L-L-LET'S PRETEND
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YEAH.
OKAY... SCARF'S DONE.
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON.
OKAY.
HI.
HEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
ROSS HAS SOME
BIG THING TO
TELL EVERYONE.
UH... UH, OKAY...
IT'S, UH...
EMILY AND I...
WE DECIDED TO, UH...
TO GET MARRIED.
WHAT?!
OH! ARE YOU PREGNANT, TOO?
UH, NO.
WHEN... WHEN DID...?
HOW... HOW DID YOU...?
WE-WE JUST DECIDED
TO... TO GO FOR IT.
I MEAN, WE KNOW
IT'S A BIT HASTY
BUT, UH...
IT JUST FEELS SO RIGHT, SO...
UM... I WAS JUST TELLING
THE GUYS...
YEAH. I... I HEARD.
I THINK IT'S GREAT!
I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU.
WELL, YEAH... CONGRATULATIONS.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
OH, MY GOD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE GETTING MARRIED.
YEAH.
MONICA AND RACHEL
MADE OUT.
Singing Guy:
♪ MORNING'S HERE ♪
♪ THE MORNING'S HERE ♪
Both:
♪ SUNSHINE IS HERE ♪
♪ THE SKY IS CLEAR ♪
♪ THE MORNING'S HERE... ♪
HEY! YOU'RE BACK!
HEY!
♪ GET INTO GEAR ♪
♪ BREAKFAST IS NEAR ♪
♪ THE DARK OF NIGHT
HAS DISAPPEARED ♪
I'LL SEE YOU
TOMORROW MORNING.
OKAY.